A Guide to the Faculty Senate Records, 1966-1990
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Minutes, 1982. (Box-folder 5-370)
- Minutes: Cabinet, 1982. (Box-folder 5-371)
- Miscellaneous, 1982. (Box-folder 5-372)
- Reductions in Force, 1982. (Box-folder 5-373)
- Remarks to the 1982 Administrators' Conference: Konrad Kubin, 1982. (Box-folder 5-374)
- Report: Ad Hoc Committee on Procedures for Resolving Faculty Disputes, 1982. (Box-folder 5-375)
- Resolutions, 1982. (Box-folder 5-376)
- Roster, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 5-377)
- Student Leaders' Bibliography, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 5-378)
- Affirmative Action 1/2, 1983. (Box-folder 5-379)
- Affirmative Action 2/2, 1983. (Box-folder 5-380)
- Constitution and Bylaws of the College of Agriculture and Life Sciences Faculty Association, 1983. (Box-folder 5-381)
- Correspondence, 1983. (Box-folder 5-382)
- Early Quarter System, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 5-383)
- Implementing the Core Curriculum, 1983. (Box-folder 5-384)
- Minutes 1/2, 1983. (Box-folder 5-385)
- Minutes 2/2, 1983. (Box-folder 5-386)
- Minutes: Cabinet, 1983. (Box-folder 5-387)
- Minutes: Commission on Graduate Studies, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 5-388)
- Minutes: University Council, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 5-389)
- Miscellaneous, 1983. (Box-folder 5-390)
- Promotion and Tenure, 1983. (Box-folder 5-390)
- Report: Academic Aspects of Athletics at Virginia Tech, April 1983. (Box-folder 5-392)
- Resolutions, 1983. (Box-folder 5-393)
- Campaign for Excellence, 1984. (Box-folder 5-394)
- Correspondence, 1984. (Box-folder 5-395)
- Elections and Nominations, 1984. (Box-folder 5-396)
- Membership on University Committees, Commissions, Etc. 1984-1985. (Box-folder 5-397)
- Minutes, 1984. (Box-folder 5-398)
- Minutes: Cabinet, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 5-399)
- Minutes: Commission on Student Affairs, 1984. (Box-folder 5-400)
- Miscellaneous, 1984. (Box-folder 5-401)
- Proposed Calendar Resolutions, 1984. (Box-folder 5-402)
- Questionnaire on Employment of Faculty Spouses, 1984. (Box-folder 5-403)
- Report: Ad Hoc Committee on Affirmative Action, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 5-404)
- Report: Honor System Review Board, 1984. (Box-folder 5-405)
- Report: Honor System Review Board, 1984. (Box-folder 5-406)
- Roster and Other Organizational Papers, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 5-407)
- Salary Analysis, August 24, 1984. (Box-folder 5-408)
- CGA Teacher/Course Evaluation Proposal, 1984. (Box-folder 5-409)
- Academy of University Service, 1985. (Box-folder 6-410)
- Affirmative Action/Equal Opportunity, 1985. (Box-folder 6-411)
- Campaign for Excellence, 1985. (Box-folder 6-412)
- Correspondence 1/3, 1985. (Box-folder 6-412a)
- Correspondence 2/3, 1985. (Box-folder 6-413)
- Correspondence 3/3, 1985. (Box-folder 6-414)
- Elections and Nominations, 1985. (Box-folder 6-415)
- Exit Interviews of Graduating Seniors, Comparison with 1983, 1985. (Box-folder 6-416)
- Faculty Senate of Virginia, 1985. (Box-folder 6-417)
- Finances, 1985. (Box-folder 6-418)
- Interest Form, 1985. (Box-folder 6-419)
- Microcomputers at Virginia Tech: Policy, Procedures, and Practices, 1985. (Box-folder 6-420)
- Minutes, 1985. (Box-folder 6-420a)
- Minutes: Cabinet, 1985. (Box-folder 6-412b)
- Miscellaneous, 1985. (Box-folder 6-421)
- Policy on Intellectual Property, 1985. (Box-folder 6-422)
- Proposal: Two-year Agricultural Technology Associate Degree Program, August 1985. (Box-folder 6-423)
- Report: Ad Hoc Committee on Measures to Minimize Undergraduate Attrition, 1985. (Box-folder 6-424)
- Report: College and University Associate Category, 1985. (Box-folder 6-425)
- Report: Commission on Undergraduate Studies: Foreign Language Requirement and Related, 1985. (Box-folder 6-426)
- Report: A Comparison of the Policies of Selected Peer Institutions..., 1985. (Box-folder 6-427)
- Report: Fan Behavior Committee: Tech Pride through Sportsmanship, 1985. (Box-folder 6-428)
- Report: Management: Peter Rony, 1985. (Box-folder 6-429)
- Report: University Benefits Committee, 1985. (Box-folder 6-430)
- Resolutions, 1985. (Box-folder 6-431)
- Review Committee, 1985. (Box-folder 6-432)
- Rosters, 1985. (Box-folder 6-433)
- Faculty Salary Study, 1985. (Box-folder 6-434)
- SGA Goals and Objectives, 1985. (Box-folder 6-435)
- Traffic Committee, 1985. (Box-folder 6-436)
- Academy of Faculty Service, 1986. (Box-folder 6-437)
- Accuracy in Media Report, 1986. (Box-folder 6-438)
- Announcements/Memoranda, 1986. (Box-folder 6-439)
- Athletic Admissions, 1986. (Box-folder 6-440)
- Athletic Director Hiring, 1986. (Box-folder 6-441)
- Blueprint Committee on Athletics, 1986. (Box-folder 6-442)
- Board of Visitors Meeting: Academic Affairs Committee, 1986. (Box-folder 6-443)
- College Self-Study Committee, 1986. (Box-folder 6-444)
- Committee on Reconciliation, 1986. (Box-folder 6-445)
- Conference on the Academic Profession, 1986. (Box-folder 6-446)
- Conference on Nuclear Winter, 1986. (Box-folder 6-447)
- Constitution and Bylaws, 1986. (Box-folder 6-448)
- Constitution of the Virginia Tech Honor System, 1986. (Box-folder 6-449)
- Correspondence 1/2, 1986. (Box-folder 6-450)
- Correspondence 2/2, 1986. (Box-folder 6-451)
- CUS Resolution 85-86B: Entrance Requirements, 1986. (Box-folder 6-452)
- Early Retirement, 1986-1988. (Box-folder 6-453)
- Elections/Nominations 1/2, 1986. (Box-folder 6-454)
- Elections/Nominations 2/2, 1986. (Box-folder 6-455)
- Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action, 1986. (Box-folder 6-456)
- Faculty Review Committee, 1986. (Box-folder 6-457)
- Faculty Senate of Virginia: Minutes, 1986. (Box-folder 6-458)
- Faculty Senate of Virginia: Questionnaire, 1986. (Box-folder 6-459)
- Financial, 1986. (Box-folder 6-460)
- Freshman Rule, 1986. (Box-folder 6-461)
- Honorifics Committee, 1986. (Box-folder 6-462)
- Library Organization Changes, 1986. (Box-folder 6-463)
- Minutes, 1986. (Box-folder 7-464)
- Miscellaneous, 1986. (Box-folder 7-465)
- Past President Address: Paul Smeal, 1986. (Box-folder 7-466)
- Past Presidents Meeting, 1986. (Box-folder 7-467)
- Presentation by David Roselle: Computing Issues and Strategies at Virginia Tech, 1986. (Box-folder 7-468)
- Procedures for Visitors at Meetings, 1986. (Box-folder 7-469)
- Report to Board of Visitors, 1986. (Box-folder 7-470)
- Report: Committee on Identity and Image, 1986. (Box-folder 7-471)
- Report: The Search for More Effective State Policy Leadership in Higher Education, 1986. (Box-folder 7-472)
- Rosters and Organizational Charts, 1986. (Box-folder 7-473)
- 1986-1987 Self Study: Major Issues and Recommendations, 1986. (Box-folder 7-474)
- SGA Minutes, 1986. (Box-folder 7-475)
- Sporn Award, 1986. (Box-folder 7-476)
- Traffic Committee, 1986. (Box-folder 7-477)
- Annual Report of the President of the Faculty Senate, 1987. (Box-folder 7-478)
- Commissions, Committees, and Council Representatives, 1987. (Box-folder 7-479)
- Committee on Intellectual Property: Nominations, 1987. (Box-folder 7-480)
- Correspondence,1987. (Box-folder 7-481)
- Elections and Nomination, 1987. (Box-folder 7-482)
- Faculty Retreat, 1987. (Box-folder 7-483)
- Faculty Senate of Virginia, 1987. (Box-folder 7-484)
- Interest From, 1987. (Box-folder 7-485)
- Meetings of College Faculty Associations, 1987. (Box-folder 7-486)
- Minutes, 1987. (Box-folder 7-487)
- Miscellaneous, 1987. (Box-folder 7-488)
- Miscellaneous Agendas and Minutes, 1987. (Box-folder 7-489)
- Name of the University, 1987. (Box-folder 7-490)
- Policy on Sexual Harassment, 1987. (Box-folder 7-491)
- Recommendations of Senate Presidents' Roundtable, 1987. (Box-folder 7-492)
- Report: CFA Retirement Questionnaire Results, 1987-1988. (Box-folder 7-493)
- Report: Commission on Research: Goals and Objectives for Research, 1987. (Box-folder 7-494)
- Report: Outcome Assessment Task Force, 1987. (Box-folder 7-495)
- Resolutions, 1987. (Box-folder 4-796)
- Roster, 1987. (Box-folder 7-497)
- Scheduling and Registration Committee, 1987. (Box-folder 7-498)
- Sporn Award, 1987. (Box-folder 7-499)
- Staff Questionnaire, 1987. (Box-folder 7-500)
- Statement on Intercollegiate Athletics, 1987. (Box-folder 7-501)
- Student Assessment Guidelines, 1987. (Box-folder 7-502)
- Virginia Tech Honor System, 1987. (Box-folder 7-503)
- Bylaws and Constitutions, 1988. (Box-folder 7-504)
- Elections, 1988. (Box-folder 7-505)
- Minutes, 1988. (Box-folder 7-506)
- Procedures of the Faculty Review Committee, 1988. (Box-folder 7-507)
- Representatives on University Council, Commissions, Committees, 1988. (Box-folder 7-508)
- Articles of Incorporation: Waste Policy Institute, 1989. (Box-folder 7-509)
- Constitution: Vote on Changes, 1989. (Box-folder 7-510)
- Forum: The University of the 21st Century, 1989. (Box-folder 7-511)
- Minutes, 1989. (Box-folder 7-512)
- Minutes, 1990. (Box-folder 7-513)